Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
M_I_SForEver
Let it go!
Can't hold it back anymore
Turn away and slam the door
I don't care
What they're going to say
Let the storm rage on
The cold never bothered me anyway
What's happening?
I'm alive!
Who said that?
I said that.
I can talk. I can think. I can juggle.
No, I cannot.
I got too confident there.
I appear to be some sort of snowman.
How absurd is that?
How is that even possible?
What am I even saying? Who am I?
Hello? Anybody there?
I'm having a bit of
a crisis of identity, I think.
So, I'm made of snow
and I'm walking on snow.
Oh, that's kind of weird.
I think I'm lost and confused.
I'm definitely confused.
Reindeers are better than people
Barn songs.
Hello? Anybody missing a snowman?
Yoo-hoo!
Welcome to Wandering Oaken's.
Ooh!
Wandering Oaken's?
Do you know that if you
scramble up those letters,
- it's an anagram for Naked Norwegians?
- Mmm?
Oh!
And I can't even read.
I genuinely don't know
how I just did that.
You know what? I like you.
What do you need?
A sense of self.
I don't even know my name.
I kind of look like a Fernando...
or a Trevor.
And where's my nose?
- You want a nose?
- Yes. But I don't have any money.
That's okay.
That's very generous, fuzzy man bear.
Do you have any, uh, carrots?
Oh. I just sold my last ones.
But I'm sure we can find you something
that will fit the bill.
Ooh! Ow!
Uh... Mmm-mmm.
What is this?
- That would be of summer.
- Summer?
It's beautiful!
Hey... Uh... Oh!
Bees buzzing!
This is sun! Butterflies!
Ooh! Blue skies!
Ah!
Oh!
I've never identified with anything
so much in my whole life.
It's like snowmen and summer
just belong together.
Oh, I'm not so sure about that.
But if it's summer you like,
I've just the nose for you.
A sausage?
A summer sausage.
- Ya!
- Ooh!
Thank you, big, loveable,
pink-faced bear man.
I'm off to find my name!
Ah, what a nose!
Processed meat.
Stay away!
Since when do wolves eat meat? Ahhh!
I'm falling apart!
Is this a skill or a flaw?
Skill! Skill!
Flaw!
You got engaged to someone
you just met that day?
Whoa!
Everybody, stay together.
Use the buddy system.
Have you seen our butt?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
No! No! No!
Back together again at...
You have friends who are love experts?
I'm not buying it.
- Stop talking.
- No, no, no. No, no.
- I'd like to meet these...
- No, I mean it.
Get ready to jump, Sven!
Yes! No!
Hmm?
Maybe it's still...
Huh?
You need this even more than I do.
Here you go.
Aw!
That felt just like a warm hug.
Do you wanna build a snowman?
Do the magic!
I'm Olaf and I like warm hugs.
I never knew winter
could be so beautiful.
Skill!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org